So, this is a crazy story about how life
comes full circle that deserves to be
mentioned. When I was 19, I fled
barefooted and shirtless from police in
Lincoln County, Georgia and ran 20 mi
that night, got away, and nobody saw me
for almost 20 months. When I was in the
streets in 2008, an economic distress in
America, I had to work construction cuz
I had no license, no ID, no nothing. And
that's where I first began construction
work. I'm the only construction worker
in my entire family. Then, when they
finally caught me, I went to prison for
30 months at Roger State Prison, where I
started learning Spanish with the locos,
and the Mexicans there, they really
taught me, man. I became friends with
them. I was the only white boy allowed
on the soccer field. Now, fast forward
15 years from my prison release. I'm
currently building something in a
Spanish-speaking country known as Costa
Rica. You see how life comes full
circle? Just remember, it's not what
happens to you, it's what you do with
it. And here's a Joe Fails quote, "If
you put your foot on my head, I will
roll sideways." I was running from the
law, I learned a new skill. you
put me in prison, learn another skill,
and then later I will apply it to things
that I never thought possible because
the unspeakable happened to me. Go chase
your dreams, you never know where they
might take you, even in bad times.